Previously on "The Rookie"...
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
Honeymoon day one.
I just wanted
a normal honeymoon.
Time's up. Boot.
You find a place to live?
Let me introduce you
to my new landlord.
Spill it.
What's going on
with you and Lucy?
She's taking
the sergeant's exam.
So you two can
get back together.
I've been doing
a lot of thinking.
OK.
And you should move in
with me so we can give us a...
a real shot.
Simply put. the U.S.
government has been leveraged.
Leveraged by who?
-Monica.
-Miss me?
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
♪ Sundown.
calling your name ♪
♪ Heading uptown.
switching up lanes ♪
♪ Bright lights.
watching them shine ♪
♪ Into the night ♪
♪ I can't think about ♪
♪ Anything
but your affection ♪
♪ All caught up
in this obsession ♪
♪ Hold up. wait up ♪
They just landed at the hotel.
Good.
♪ I got one shot.
can't stop ♪
♪ Man on a mission ♪
♪ Girl. I'm bringing it
all to you ♪
Good afternoon.
I am FBI Supervisory
Special Agent Matthew Garza.
and this is
Detective Nyla Harper
from the Los Angeles
Police Department.
Now. we are D-day.
H-hour on a fast-moving.
multi-country operation.
All the luggage together. please.
Reservation under Stevens.
You know.
I still don't understand
why I can't have my own room.
Yes. you do.
#We Don't Trust You.
As part of her immunity deal.
Monica Stevens has agreed
to help the FBI. LAPD.
and Interpol
track down and arrest
several high-value criminal
and terrorist targets
operating inside
and outside the United States.
You know. here I thought
I was doing you a favor.
getting you a European vacation
on America's dime.
Yes. because your sense
of charity is legendary.
Fine.
You know. be a hater.
But whether
you believe it or not.
I am here solely
to help law enforcement
get a legendary weapons
trafficker off the streets.
Yeah. we're still going
to watch you like a hawk.
Given Monica's
unrepentant duplicity.
we have assigned
officer John Nolan
and Lieutenant Bailey Nune
to babysit.
Our first target...
Lukas Wegner.
Some of you are
already aware of Wegner.
He's had a red notice
since 2023 for selling
FIM-92J Stinger missiles.
as well as a dozen outstanding
arrest warrants in California.
Monica contacted Wegner
last week
on behalf of a fictional buyer
to arrange
a pass-through purchase
of a battalion's worth
of heavy weapons.
Their meeting has yet to be set.
but SIGINT suggests
that Wegner is coming
into town tomorrow.
It is known that he travels
with a hardcore security detail.
so we're going to need
this takedown
to be fast and overwhelming.
Simultaneously. the LAPD. MI5.
and Berlin Police
will be executing raids
on Wegner's operations
in their respective cities.
All in all. this needs to be
the smoothest operation
any of us have ever pulled off.
And it all relies on our ability
to control Monica Stevens.
the poster child
for chaos theory.
So say a prayer.
♪ Man on a mission ♪
Oh.
I'm taking the bigger room.
-Hey.
-Just let her.
We're going to be
sleeping in shifts anyway.
Uh. would you...
in the other room?
Dekuju.
Thank you.
You know. Monica is not wrong.
We could add a few days
onto the back
of our assignment here
and turn this trip
into a real second honeymoon.
I love it.
I mean. clearly.
we're going to have to find
a cheaper hotel room.
but I love it.
Is that velvet?
Hey.
How was the night shift?
Three words:
strippers versus clowns.
So many questions.
starting with. how. why.
and. uh. who won?
Who knows?
And. I mean.
the strippers. obviously.
And for the record.
a crying clown is.
in fact. the creepiest clown.
Great.
Well. I'm just finishing up
a workout before my shift.
Want to join?
It'll help balance you
before bed.
I really should.
I mean. unless you need
to save your energy
for an early morning booty call.
Please.
That is not happening.
Wait. Tim still hasn't
asked you out
now that you're
fellow sergeants?
Nope.
I mean. what the hell?
It's been three days since
he made you a feast and left.
Well. to be fair.
I did fall asleep.
It doesn't matter.
It's not OK
to leave you hanging.
I'm going to talk to him.
No. don't do that.
Then you should.
Seriously. I love you both.
but you have
the same exact problem.
You suck at having
hard conversations.
I do not.
OK. look. what if
Lucy falling asleep
was the universe
sending me a sign
that I was moving too fast
asking her to move in with me?
The universe?
You sound like Celina.
God forbid.
Do not knock that girl.
She's in touch with her feelings
and a great communicator.
whereas you suck.
You said that already.
Listen to me.
Nature abhors a vacuum.
So if you don't take care
of your relationship. I will.
Well. short of hanging
a bell around Monica's neck.
she's locked down tight
for the night.
How's the task force going?
So far. everyone is working
and playing well together.
-Hey. mama. How's Prague?
-Stunning.
The food is a little
cream heavy for my taste.
but I'm still eating
way too much of it.
Has James called yet for help?
Nope. He's a pro.
Got those kids all squared away.
All right. all right.
Can we focus
on the task at hand. please?
I will call you later.
Things are moving quickly here.
Wegner could call
to set the meeting
for as soon as tomorrow.
That could be a problem.
We haven't been able to locate
Wegner's main base of
operations.
I thought we had solid intel
that he was working
out of the Port of Los Angeles.
We do. but the port is
7.500 acres
with 25 cargo terminals.
15 marinas. and 5 rail yards.
Like trying to find
a baby tick on a mule deer.
I don't get that analogy.
Oh. you see. mule deers are big.
and baby ticks are small.
-Enough.
-OK.
I hate to say move faster.
but move faster.
If we take out Wegner but
leave U.S. leadership in place.
his network and those weapons
will live on without him.
Understood.
We'll dig in.
Good.
All right. so what's the plan?
Shake the trees harder.
see if we can get a location.
If we do that.
we risk alerting Wegner
that we're looking.
You got a better idea?
I bet good money Wegner's got
people working at the port.
you know. eyes and ears
to keep their operations safe.
That's actually
a solid idea. Smitty.
I have my moments.
I can pull mug shots
for all known associates.
Then we stake up the port.
grab up
the first recognizable face.
All right. good.
Do it.
Everybody get in plain clothes
and be ready
for some serious OT.
Now let's get to it.
Hey. kid.
Got a minute?
-I really don't. sir.
-Great.
Listen. I wanted
to give you a heads-up.
Shangri-La is starting an HOA.
and there's going to be a fee.
Hold on... the parking lot
we all sleep in
is starting
a homeowners association?
That's what I just said.
And you're going
to start charging me rent?
No. not rent.
It's a fee to live there.
That's what...
how much is this fee?
900 a month.
900?
Now. I know
that seems like a lot.
but there's going to be
a ton of upgrades.
Boot. snap to it.
-You got profiles to pull.
-Yes. sir. Sorry.
We'll talk about this later.
I'm marking you down as a yes.
No. you're not.
Agree to disagree.
They're all clean.
Yeah. or they're just
not in our system.
So...
If you're going to ask me
about Lucy. don't.
No. I wasn't.
It's just Smitty's planning
to start charging me rent.
He can't do that. right?
His cousin is the department's
facilities manager.
Meaning?
Meaning he controls
every station parking lot
in Los Angeles.
So if I say no. what. he...
Smitty kicks me out?
Wait. hold on.
I know that face.
-Green hat?
-Yeah. green hat.
That's Christian Lobo.
Street team. be advised.
suspect Christian Lobo is
on his way out to you.
Hispanic male.
6 feet. 180 pounds.
Black T-shirt. blue jeans.
Currently on parole
for assault with a deadly.
He's driving a blue Toyota.
license plate 3 Ida David
William 674.
He's heading out now.
Copy that. 7-Adam-100.
Operation Bottleneck
is in motion.
Remember. we need to grab
Lobo before he can make a call
and alert the others.
Don't worry.
I sweet talked the gear heads
into lending us
a cell phone jammer.
As soon as we see the car.
we'll hit him with it.
As long as he's within 50 yards.
his phone's a paperweight.
No. baby.
I'm never tired of you.
I just gotta hit the crib.
make myself pretty.
Come on. baby. you know
you're pretty no matter what.
I kind of like you
all dirty and...
The target has arrived.
Just get that fine ass
over here.
-Babe?
-All right. he's jammed.
Let's go.
Police!
Show me your hands!
We lost containment.
Lobo is heading west on Beacon.
We can't let him get
out of jammer range.
Go.
Come on!
-He's getting away.
-No. he's not.
-Do not let him get away.
-I'm not!
Go!
Come on!
We've got a priority 1 case
for an ex lap
the second an OR frees up.
Ready?
One. two. three.
Hey.
I need to talk to him.
-Yeah. when we're done.
-No. now.
He needs surgery.
You can question him later.
I am questioning him now.
What is going on?
This patient has information
that is time critical
to a major operation.
Getting him into surgery
is what's time critical.
You don't even have
an OR yet. Doctor.
Wait.
You're going to need to wait.
I can't.
Hey. son. answer one question.
and I'll let them take you
to surgery.
Wait. This is our patient.
If you do not allow us
to treat him.
I will have to file a complaint.
Just get away from my patient.
Give me a minute!
Give me a minute.
Which terminal does Wegner use
to store weapons?
-I can't.
-You can.
Wait.
You tell me now.
and we won't press charges.
-Wade. stop.
-Tell me.
OR 2 is open.
Tell me!
APM.
Take him.
Let's go. Let's go!
Check his airway.
I can't believe you did that.
Did he give you anything?
Yeah. although I'm definitely
sleeping on the couch
for the next six months.
Wegner operates
out of the APM terminal.
Great.
What section?
It's 400 acres.
It's better
than what we had before.
Get your surveillance team
in place.
And take Wesley with you.
Why?
He's scrappy. but he's not
much help in an armed conflict.
If this goes to trial.
Wegner is going to have
an army of lawyers.
We need to make sure our side
of the street is spotless.
Yes. sir.
Any word on when the Prague
meeting will take place?
Not yet. but they're
working around the clock.
Good morning.
I was just going
to grab a coffee downstairs.
And you didn't want to wake us.
So sweet.
John. isn't Monica
just so thoughtful?
Does it count if you
only think about yourself?
This is ridiculous.
Do you really expect me
to sit around
waiting for Wegner's call?
-Yes.
-Yeah.
You know. Prague
is one of the most beautiful
cities in the world.
Don't you want to see it?
I mean. kind of.
Our job is to keep
an eye on her.
No one ever said where.
We're in the middle of an
international sting operation.
-We're not going sightseeing.
-Why not?
Because if Wegner is
having you watched.
seeing you with us
could spook him.
Easy.
You're my assistant.
and you're my bodyguard.
Honestly. it would be
more suspicious
if I was seen walking around
without an entourage.
That works.
Fine. but only for an hour.
Before we go anywhere.
you need new clothes.
Everyone who works for me
needs a certain level
of sophistication.
Even the hired muscle.
What's wrong with what I wear?
You look great.
It's just not.
like. sophisticated.
Hi.
I need a few things sent up.
Come right in.
♪ This way. let it play ♪
What is happening?
Concierge reached out
to a few boutiques
on our behalf.
explained how much
we value our privacy.
Is this how rich people shop?
Oh. this is nice.
Oh. that color
is perfect for you.
Try these.
I can choose my own clothes.
thank you very much.
-Ooh. try this.
-Yes. dear.
♪ Shake it up ♪
Hop to it.
Absolutely not.
♪ Come on. let me see ya ♪
Right.
Well. this one's not bad.
Are you sure
that's not a woman's coat?
That's a no.
♪ I'm the cream
of the crop ♪
♪ Make your head spin ♪
Turn around.
This is giving more nightclub.
Oof.
I don't know that I can pull off
this much reptile.
Change.
♪ Ding-dang. big bang.
I been on a mission ♪
Hmm.
Maybe with a different...
No.
No more outfits.
No more opinions.
This is it.
I guess it'll have to do.
How are you paying
for all this. anyway?
You've been on the run
for a year.
We'll charge it to the room.
which the government is
paying for.
By the time they get the bill.
the operation
will have been a success
and all will be forgiven.
For you. maybe.
I will most certainly
get yelled at.
I'd call that a win-win.
Shall we?
Let's go.
We have eyes in the sky.
Teams check in.
7-Lincoln-13 in position
2331 in position.
7-Lincoln-9 in the hizzy.
Hizzy?
What is this. 1992?
Ignore him.
All personnel. tag anyone
who comes and goes.
We have off-campus units
ready to check tails.
-Copy.
Fo shizzle.
Fo shizzle?
I mean. was he dropped
on his head as a child?
Repeatedly would be my guess.
So what do we do now?
We just sit here?
Stakeouts can be an opportunity
for people to really talk.
discuss their issues.
Is there something
that we need to talk about?
No.
Good.
We're not the problem.
-Hold this.
-What?
You'll be good.
Uh. Angela. where are you going?
OK.
What are you doing?
Miles. Celina needs help.
Sure thing.
With what?
-Snacks.
-Got it.
Oh. uh. what kind of snacks?
What is this?
Have you talked to Lucy yet?
No.
I'm working and she's asleep.
That's not an excuse.
No. it's two.
Also. we have a job to do.
and I outrank you.
I told you.
nature abhors a vacuum.
Why are you so scared
to talk to her?
I'm not. OK?
It just needs to be
the right time.
You're putting way too much
pressure on this.
I know you're terrified
of screwing up again.
but you can't let it
paralyze you.
-I'm not.
-You are.
And I get it.
You sabotaged
your relationship with Lucy
to punish yourself
for your failures.
But you worked through all that.
So it's time to get out
of your head and into your...
And "into my heart"? Yeah.
You mock. but that's
exactly what you need.
Heads up.
Wegner's crew has landed.
terminal K.
We have a target. people.
So how exactly
did you get your hands
on top secret intel
to leverage against
the U.S. government?
Mm. I shouldn't say.
But you will. because you need
to show us how smart you are.
I do not.
But I am.
Do you remember
that bus hijacking?
-That was you?
-Mm-hmm.
I was on that bus.
-We were on that bus.
-Oh. I know.
When I heard. I was sure
the LAPD was onto me.
No. it was just dumb luck.
So you hired
that fake pregnant lady?
Why?
All I can say. without revealing
classified information. is that
the NSA used to allow employees
with eyes-only
security clearance
to ride public transportation.
What?
We're being followed.
You think he works for Wegner?
We have other options?
You make many enemies
in Eastern Europe?
I mean. who hasn't?
That's not helpful.
How do you want to play it?
I say we do nothing.
If he is one of Wegner's guys.
then he's just making sure
his boss isn't walking
into a trap.
We continue to play the part
of Monica's entourage.
And if it's not Wegner's guy?
I guess we'll find out soon.
You want to force it a little?
Luxury Prague vacation lacking
enough excitement for you?
No.
Well...
-Bailey.
-I know.
I have a problem.
Now what?
OK. you didn't have
to get one of everything.
Well. Lopez made it
seem like an emergency.
and Tim said we're going
to be here all night. so...
You know Lopez just
wanted you out of the van
so she could talk to Tim. right?
I know that now.
Hey. what's up?
We need to talk.
-Back to the van.
-Yes. ma'am.
We need to deal with this
Tim and Lucy situation.
Yes. thank you.
It is driving me insane.
Same.
Here's what I'm thinking.
Is the op blown?
Maybe. maybe not.
He didn't have any ID on him.
and he's not talking.
other than a blizzard
of curse words.
I don't think he's with Wegner.
Wegner's a cautious man.
If he suspected
that I sold him out.
he'd just ghost me
and then have me killed
six months from now
when no one was watching.
Which means that this guy
was sent by somebody else
who hates you enough
to assassinate you
in broad daylight?
Yep.
Yeah. that doesn't surprise me.
You are uniquely hate able.
Oh. you're sweet.
I'll run him through all
the international databases.
see if we can get some clarity
as to who he's working for.
Everyone. quiet.
Mr. Wegner.
You know. I was just beginning
to wonder if my business trip
had sadly become a vacation.
I had to make sure
I had the items
you were looking for in stock.
I take it that this call
means that you do?
You failed to mention
when we first spoke
that you're a wanted woman
back in the States.
I figured. in our line of work.
outstanding warrants are
a given.
You have a red notice yourself.
if I'm not mistaken.
Well. that's true.
Bottom line is. I have skin
in the game. Mr. Wegner.
which makes me
extremely motivated.
I need this deal to go smoothly.
which makes me
a perfect customer.
So shall we set a meeting.
finalize the deal?
Café de Luna. 4:00 PM.
All right.
we don't have much time.
I want schematics for that café
and the surrounding streets.
Put the SOG team on alert
and find them
a staging area nearby.
Come on. let's go.
All right. I will alert
law enforcement
in London. Berlin. and LA
to be ready
to raid Wegner's operation
the second we give them
the signal.
-Let's go.
-Let's do it.
Smitty. why are you calling me?
Bring the snacks
over this way. Texas.
You're supposed
to be watching the bad guys.
not me. Smitty.
I'm doing both.
Ah.
Mm-hmm.
Not a bad selection.
Take as much as you want.
Great.
So I know you're on the fence
about the HOA.
Yeah. the Shangri-La parking
lot belongs to the city.
-You can't charge people rent.
-It's not rent.
It's dues for all the amenities
we've added.
-Like what?
-Like a hot tub. for one.
You can't build a hot tub
in a city parking lot.
It's inflatable.
What better way to relax
after a hard day on the job?
Bunch of guys drinking beer.
watching the big screen.
In a standing tub of hot water
that's never
filtered or drained.
That's what chlorine's for.
Strike team.
Dream Team landing in five
to supplement the raid.
Metro is finalizing POA.
will be on site in 40.
More to follow.
Hey.
Hi.
We need to talk.
Look. I'm sorry I put you
in that situation.
You got dangerously close
to violating that man's
civil rights
and destroying your career.
not to mention putting us
at risk for being sued
for everything we own.
You know better.
There were
life and death stakes.
This is a global operation.
Luna.
But I could have
handled it better.
so I'm sorry.
OK?
Now let's talk about it
when I get home.
When was the last time
we were both home and awake
at the same moment?
Hey. I clock out
at the same time I always have.
This is an exception.
So it's my job.
That's the problem.
I really don't want
to do this right now.
I'm not giving up my job.
And I'm not asking you to.
just like I didn't ask you to
when Dominique was born.
I know.
And I was happy to stay home.
Those years were
the greatest joy of my life.
But I was left in limbo
when Dominique went
off to college.
waiting for you to retire.
which you never did.
So I stopped waiting.
and I moved on with my life.
I love my new career.
I love being more
than just a wife and a mom.
I have to make it my priority.
Even if it means
we rarely see each other?
Understood.
-Hey.
Reinforcements have arrived.
Yay!
-Thank you.
-Yep.
-How's it going?
-Good. Long night.
-Yeah.
Target is
the G container corridor.
That's where Wegner's team
has set up shop.
Raid starts in 30 minutes.
if everything goes
according to plan in Prague.
Oh. and. uh. Tim needs you
in the surveillance van.
200 yards to the south.
Just as long as you stay
to the east.
you are out of sight
from our target.
OK.
Do you know
what he needs me for?
Sergeant business.
OK.
Hey.
Lopez needs you.
Why'd she text you and not me?
No idea.
Hey. what's going on?
Angela and your roommate
have too much free time.
Oh.
They wanted to get us alone.
-I'm sorry.
-No. it's fine.
I mean. they're right.
We do need to talk.
Yeah. let's... come on.
Well. I guess
I should start by apologizing.
Strongly agree.
It's been. like. three days.
I know.
I should have called sooner.
I just... I was scared.
What if we get back together
and it's not like it was before?
Even worse. what if you realize
you don't love the new.
less toxic me?
Trust me. becoming
emotionally healthier.
that... that is...
that's a turn-on.
not the opposite.
So you're not worried?
Of course I'm worried.
You broke my heart.
The scar is so deep.
it might never fade.
But. you know. I'm hoping
that it'll make us stronger.
You know. we both know
what we lost.
Hopefully we'll fight
to make it work.
We will.
I love you.
I love you too.
OK. now ask me out.
No. No.
No. I... I actually wasn't.
um. going to ask you out.
I want to ask you
to move in with me.
I've spent enough nights
without you
that I want you
all the way in my life.
Is that right?
Yeah.
So is... is that a yes?
Oh. God.
Do you promise to be
a better communicator?
Oh. yes.
I mean. I promise
to be the best communicator.
not a single thought
that I will keep to myself.
-Shh.
-Ever.
Just say yes. please.
Yes.
Where are the keys?
Do you think
Monica gets nervous?
I do.
I mean. I know
she likes to project
that whole apex predator vibe.
but. uh.
still a human being
inside there.
-I'm saying. deep inside.
-Disagree.
Monica is pure lizard brain
in designer heels.
always working the angle
for her number one client...
herself.
Can I get you anything else
while you wait?
You know. I can't pass up
a Romanée-Conti.
An excellent choice.
Yeah. and only
1.000 bucks a bottle.
Oh. you should see
the clothing bill
the hotel sent over.
OK. I'm going to pretend like
I didn't hear that. for now.
I'm guessing this is Wegner.
Yeah. that's him.
Everybody. get ready.
LA team. move into position.
Take them down on my mark.
LA team in position.
Mr. Wegner.
Your mug shot
doesn't do you justice.
Oh. I should hope not.
Looks like
I'm under investing in security.
Or perhaps you just pick
quality over quantity.
Would you like me to stay?
No.
Let the grown-ups talk.
Are you staying in Prague long?
We got five hostiles.
all packing heat.
I don't know. it could get
messy with all these civilians.
Should we wait to grab Wegner
after the meeting?
That's a negative.
Those are armored SUVs.
We need to hold our nerve
and get this thing done.
I'm estimating SWAT needs
about 6 seconds
to close the gap
and make the arrest.
That's an affirmative.
Leave it to me.
Ready to move
when I say "biscuit."
-Biscuit?
The 10 million is deposited
into a dozen
Cayman Island accounts.
Once I give you the passwords.
the money is yours.
And once I have
the confirmation.
I give the order to ship.
Perfect.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to interrupt. but...
biscuit!
Go. go. go. go. go.
We are a go.
Repeat. we are a go.
Put your hands up.
Down on your knees now.
Cuff him. Boot.
Drop it.
Lucy!
Fire in the hole!
-Are you hit?
-No. no.
I just... I think I twisted
my knee when I fell.
-I'm OK.
-All right?
Yeah.
Why "biscuit"?
Yeah. I don't know.
It just popped into my head.
I think I'm hungry.
Where's Monica?
Did you get everything?
No.
Your safe deposit box
at the second bank
had been tagged by Interpol.
I pretended
like I got the number wrong
and walked away.
That was the bigger box.
Sorry.
Nothing I could do about it.
Well. what have we here?
I didn't think your type
could step on sacred ground
without bursting into flame.
You should have thrown
your phone away.
Just some personal business.
Oh!
How come you never buy me
anything like this?
I'm not a Saudi Prince.
All right. listen. I am broke.
Being on the run
for the last year
has depleted my resources.
and. uh. my immunity deal
doesn't restore my law license
or give me any money
to live off of.
If you're looking
for sympathy...
I'd settle
for some understanding.
Listen. the jewelry in that bag
I can live off of comfortably
for a year or two.
Just let me have it.
and then
we can all go home happy.
Well. sadly. that decision's
above my pay grade.
I feel like you're not
really that sad about that.
Guilty as charged.
Are you?
Hell no.
You got my husband shot.
That was not my intention.
Tell it to my ass.
Hello.
Do you owe this lady anything?
-No.
-Then we're out.
I've got her.
Nolan. we got an ID
on the assassin
you grabbed this morning.
He is not working for Wegner.
He works for Jakob Olmstead.
That's my good girl.
Mr. Olmstead.
Falconer from Argentina?
Yeah. and I doubt he sent
just one guy to do the job.
All right. we got to move.
Your Argentinean friend
is looking for payback
for bringing the Feds
to his door last year.
Move!
-We got to go up.
-Out would be better.
Yeah.
How you want to play this?
They got the numbers
and the firepower.
OK. quick hit and run.
Less talking. more escaping.
I'll take point.
I got your back.
Down!
Here.
What's the catch?
No catch.
Where are the rest
of the pieces?
OK. there is a catch.
That necklace is the only one
we were able to trace back
as a legal purchase.
so that's the only one
you get to keep.
Our appraiser estimates
it's worth 100.000.
That's enough to live on
as long as you get
a modest apartment.
In the Valley.
And you take
public transportation.
You want me to live
like a poor person?
No. I want you doing 25
to life in a federal prison.
But we all make sacrifices. right?
It's been a pleasure
working with you. as always.
Likewise.
It did feel good taking down
a Top 10 Most Wanted.
Yeah. right?
Not your usual LAPD fare.
No.
Brought me back
to my undercover days.
infiltrating
major drug operations.
In the U.S. and Mexico.
-Mexico part is classified.
-I know.
But I make it a point
of researching people
that I am trying to recruit.
You want me to join the FBI?
In the long run.
I would love that.
Right now. I'm formalizing
our multi-agency task force
to round up the rest
of Monica's list.
And I want you on board.
That is very flattering.
So what do you think?
International travel.
a generous discretionary budget.
It is tempting.
But?
I have kids
and a powerful desire
to stay married.
And I know how hard it would be
to keep my priorities straight
when my job is saving the world.
Right.
♪ Been a long time
in a low place ♪
-For me?
-No. it's for my other wife.
-She's mad at me too.
-Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
And can I give you a ride home?
I have three more patients
to check on.
but I should be home for dinner.
Really?
There's a chance.
It's OK.
Honestly. I have budget
approvals to catch up on.
And Laker game's on.
I'll put these in some water.
I... I know this is not
the next chapter
that we envisioned.
but I'm happy.
Good.
Then I am too.
♪ And those old eyes
watching me ♪
♪ But I feel safe ♪
Hey. are you still in the air?
I just landed.
There's something I need
to talk to you about.
Feel like swinging
by the airport?
This has been
the longest day of my life.
But if you and Tim
finally talked.
it was worth it.
We did.
You're moving in with him.
How did you know?
Girl. it was
in your solar return.
-I've known for months.
-Oh.
Well. listen.
I will keep paying rent
until we find someone
to take over my room.
But I think it'll all work out.
Last. best. and final...
700 a month for hot tub use
and margarita machine
privileges.
Is anyone saying yes?
Oh. yeah.
Everyone's in.
Because if you don't pay
for your HOA fees.
you're out of Shangri-La.
Told you it wouldn't take long.
Miles. before you answer.
I have a counteroffer.
Oh. I'll take it.
You haven't heard the offer yet.
I don't care.
The answer is yes.
Anything to get me
out of seventh circle of hell
that is Shangri-La.
See? It all worked out.
Well. let's talk logistics.
After everything I did for you?
Taking you in
when you had no one.
You ready to go home?
Although it's not
really my home yet.
I still have to plan a move
and...
Shh. Just say yes.
Yes.
Garza?
Thank you.
We could have met
at your office.
I'm headed straight to D.C.
I just needed to drop off
Harper and Monica
and refuel the jet.
Please. have a seat.
Thank you.
OK. color me curious.
What's the ask?
How long have you been
the watch commander
at Mid-Wilshire?
Eight years.
You feel like shaking things up?
Look. if you are happy.
no harm. no foul.
But this Monica task force is
going to consume the next year
of my life.
and I could really use
someone I trust from the LAPD
working next to me.
What does the job entail?
You'd be a senior liaison.
working out of Mid-Wilshire.
helping me oversee
all domestic operations.
Does that mean
no European adventures?
No. not at all.
I'll take as much
of your time as I can get.
You asked Harper already?
She's got a young kid.
Wouldn't be a good fit.
Look. I need an empty nester.
like you.
Now. I don't need
an answer right now.
but I will need one quick.
And I'm sure your wife is going
to have an opinion about it.
So...
Honestly. she's focused
on her next chapter.
Maybe I should do the same.
-Good?
-Good.
Safe travels.
Thank you.
Hey.
Who's going to get your job?
Well. was it worth the wait?
It was a long wait.
Just answer the question.
You're cute
when you're insecure.
It was worth the wait.
I guess we should talk about
the timeline for me moving in.
What were you going to do
if I said no?
I didn't have a plan for that.
You're adorable.
Thank you.
You're also going
to need more boxes.
Wow.
Beautiful.
So I spoke with the front desk.
Turns out
the Feds have the room booked
through the weekend.
We can stay two more days.
No additional charge.
Operation Second Honeymoon
is well underway.
This is the most
romantic moment of my life.
And we're just getting started.
Mm.
♪ Arrest me.
but make it sexy ♪
♪ Arrest me. but make it sexy ♪
♪ Arrest me.
but make it sexy ♪
Oh.
Oh. that's...
Let's just find another bridge.
Come on.
-This is the best bridge.
-It's OK.
♪ Arrest me.
but make it sexy ♪
but make it sexy. yeah ♪
Damn it.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-